Historical Audiovisual Collection, 1912-2012 (bulk 1945-1996 ): Finding Aid
Princeton University Library. Department of Rare Books and Special Collections.
- Series 5: Music, 1920-2012; 467 items
  - The Princeton University Chapel Choir with Sarah Lawrence Chorus - Christmas Vespers, 1956; 949; 1 Audio Reel(s) (Box 86)
    Harold Aks and Carl Weinrich, Conductors. 1/4 inch magnetic tape, 7-inch reel.
  - The Princeton University Chapel Choir with Mt. Holyoke Glee Club - Milbank - Handel: Israel in Egypt, 1956; 959; 2 Audio Reel(s) (Box 89)
    Milbank Memorial - C. Weinrich, Conductor. Original. 1/4 inch magnetic tape, 7-inch reel.
  - The Princeton University Chapel Choir with Mt. Holyoke Glee Club - Milbank - Handel: Israel in Egypt, 1956; 959; 2 Audio Reel(s) (Box 87)
  - The Princeton University Chapel Choir with Sarah Lawrence Choral Group - Christmas Vespers, 1956; 997; 2 Audio Reel(s) (Box 90)
  - 3 Folk Sing with Brooks Jones, Walt Winter, Ernestine Brown, 1956 May 5; AR.2017.082; 2404; 1 Phonograph Record(s) (Box 238)
  - 3 Folk Sing with Brooks Jones, Walt Winter, Ernestine Brown, 1956 May 5; AR.2017.082; 2404; 1 Disc(s) (Box 237)
    CD-R. Compact disc.
  - The Princeton Tigertones 1957-1958, 682; 1 Phonograph Record(s) (Box 60)
  - The Princeton University Chapel Choir with Vassar College Choir - Milbank - Mozart: Davidde Penitente, Bach: Christ Lag in Todesbanden, 1957; 961; 3 Audio Reel(s) (Box 87)
    Milbank Memorial Concert. 1/4 inch magnetic tape, 7-inch reel.
  - The Princeton University Chapel Choir with Vassar College Choir - Milbank - Mozart: Davidde Penitente, 1957; 986; 2 Audio Reel(s) (Box 89)
  - The Princeton University Chapel Choir with Vassar College Choir - Milbank - Bach: Cantata No. 4, 1957; 993; 1 Audio Reel(s) (Box 89)
  - The Princeton University Chapel Choir with Sarah Lawrence Chorus - Christmas Vespers, 1957; 995; 1 Audio Reel(s) (Box 90)
  - Songs of the Princeton Nassoons, 1957; AR.2006.077; 2185; 1 Phonograph Record(s) (Box 213)
  - The Princeton University Chapel Choir with Bryn Mawr Chorus - Milbank - Mozart: Vespers, Haydn: Mass in D-Minor, 1958; 964; 2 Audio Reel(s) (Box 87)
  - The Princeton University Chapel Choir with Bryn Mawr Chorus and Chamber Orchestra - Milbank - Haydn: Mass in D-Minor, 1958; 994; 1 Audio Reel(s) (Box 90)
    Milbank Memorial Concert. Reel 2 MASTER. 1/4 inch magnetic tape, 7-inch reel.
  - The Princeton University Glee Club with Harvard Glee Club - Parts IV-VI, 1958; 1185; 1 Audio Reel(s) (Box 99)
  - The Princeton University Glee Club with Columbus Boy Choir - Bach: Vivat, Vivat! (BWV205a); Sessions: Turn, O Libertad!, 1958; 1223; 1 Phonograph Record(s) (Box 59)
    Arthur Mendel and Wlater Nollner, Conductors. Created by Recorded Publications Laboratories. 33 1/3 rpm album.
  - Princeton University Glee Club, 1958-1992; 2199; 1 Phonograph Record(s) (Box 213)
    Walter Nollner, Conductor. Created by Carillon Records. 33 1/3 rpm album.
  - The Princeton University Chapel Choir - Christmas Vespers (Monteverdi: Angelus Ad Pastores Ait, Billings: A Virgin Unspotted), 1959; 951; 1 Audio Reel(s) (Box 86)
    Reel 1 of 2. 1/4 inch magnetic tape, 7-inch reel.
  - The Princeton University Chapel Choir with Smith Glee Club - Milbank - Bach: B-Minor Mass, 1959; 966; 2 Audio Reel(s) (Box 87)
  - The Princeton University Chapel Choir with Smith College Choir - Bach: B-Minor Mass (up to Credo), 1959; 996; 1 Audio Reel(s) (Box 90)
  - The Princeton University Chapel Choir - Test Series 1-5 (Motets), 1959; 1020; 1 Audio Reel(s) (Box 91)
  - The Princeton University Chapel Choir - Sunday Anthems 1958-1959 - Lassus: Oculus non Videt, 1036; 1 Audio Reel(s) (Box 92)
  - The Princeton University Chapel Choir - Easter Concert, 1959; 1039; 1 Audio Reel(s) (Box 93)
  - The Princeton University Glee Club with Sarah Lawrence College Chorus, 1959; 1159; 2 Audio Reel(s) (Box 97)
    Morley, Brahms, Debussy, Purcell, Mozart: "Idomeneo" (KV366). 1/4 inch magnetic tape, 7-inch reel.
  - The Princeton University Glee Club - Frosh Prom Concert, 1959; 1162; 2 Audio Reel(s) (Box 97)
  - The Princeton University Glee Club with Yale Glee Club, 1959; 1191; 3 Audio Reel(s) (Box 100)
  - The Princeton University Chapel Choir - Motets 1958-1959, 1234; 1 Phonograph Record(s) (Box 61)
    Carl Weinrich, Conductor. 33 1/3 rpm album.
  - The Princeton Tigertones, 1959-1960; AR.2017.082; 2405; 1 Phonograph Record(s) (Box 238)
    Created by Princeton Tigertones. 33 1/3 rpm album.
  - Christmas Greetings to 1921, 1960; 6; 1 Phonograph Record(s) (Box 58)
    Created by Gothic Studios - Princeton University Store. 33 1/3 rpm album.
  - Princeton University Band -- Going Back: The Songs of the Ivy League, 1960; 696; 1 Phonograph Record(s) (Box 60)
  - The Princeton University Chapel Choir with Sarah Lawrence Chorus - Christmas Vespers (Lassus: Judica Me, Domine), 1960; 953; 1 Audio Reel(s) (Box 86)
  - The Princeton University Chapel Choir - Sunday Anthems - Handel: Regnum Mundi, 1960; 1029; 1 Audio Reel(s) (Box 92)
  - The Princeton University Chapel Choir - Sunday Anthems 1959-1960 - Couperin: O Domine, 1037; 1 Audio Reel(s) (Box 93)
  - The Princeton University Chapel Choir - Sunday Anthems 1959-1960 - Hassler: Cantate Domino, 1038; 1 Audio Reel(s) (Box 93)
  - The Princeton University Chapel Choir - Easter Concert/Vespers - Bach: Der Herr Segne Euch, Nanino: Diffusa Est Gratia, 1960; 1040; 3 Audio Reel(s) (Box 93)
  - The Princeton University Glee Club with Smith College Chorus - Orange, NJ concert, 1960; 1101; 3 Audio Reel(s) (Box 95)
    to benefit Club Scholarship Funds. 1/4 inch magnetic tape, 7-inch reel.
  - The Princeton University Glee Club - spring 1960, 1154; 2 Audio Reel(s) (Box 97)
    recorded in Princeton Theological Seminary. 1/4 inch magnetic tape, 7-inch reel.
  - The Princeton University Glee Club with Bryn Mawr College Chorus, Princeton U. Orchestra, Brywn Mawr-Haverford Orchestra - Bach: Cantata No. 182, Brahms: Nanie, Haydn: Te Deum Laudamus, 1960; 1161; 1 Audio Reel(s) (Box 97)
    at Bryn Mawr College. 1/4 inch magnetic tape, 7-inch reel.
  - The Princeton University Glee Club - 1959-1960 season recording, 1164; 3 Audio Reel(s) (Box 98)
    Includes 2 copies of reel 2. 1/4 inch magnetic tape, 7-inch reel.
  - The Princeton University Glee Club - Haydn: To the Women, Listen to the Lambs, Knapp: Princeton Football Medley, 1960; 1168; 1 Audio Reel(s) (Box 102)
    United Community Fund concert at McCarter Theater. 1/4 inch magnetic tape, 5-inch reel.
  - The Princeton University Glee Club - Frosh Prom Concert, 1960; 1170; 2 Audio Reel(s) (Box 98)
  - The Princeton University Glee Club with Harvard Glee Club - Princeton-Harvard Football Concert, 1960; 1197; 3 Audio Reel(s) (Box 100)
  - The Princeton University Glee Club with the Princeton U. Orchestra and Bryn Mawr College Chorus - "Selections, 1959-1960 Season", 1228; 1 Phonograph Record(s) (Box 61)
    Walter Nollner, Conductor. 33 1/3 rpm album.
  - The Princeton University Chapel Choir with Sarah Lawrence Chorus - Christmas Vespers, 1961; 950; 1 Audio Reel(s) (Box 86)
  - The Princeton University Chapel Choir - Milbank - Mozart: Litaniae de Venerabili Altaris Sacramento, Schubert: Mass in E-Flat, 1961; 968; 3 Audio Reel(s) (Box 87-88)
  - The Princeton University Chapel Choir with Mt. Holyoke Glee Club - Milbank - Mozart: Litany in B-Flat, Schubert: Mass in E-Flat, 1961; 971; 3 Audio Reel(s) (Box 88)
  - The Princeton University Chapel Choir - Sunday Anthems - Tallis: I Give You a New Commandment, 1961; 1030; 1 Audio Reel(s) (Box 92)
  - The Princeton University Chapel Choir - Sunday Anthems - Couperin: O Domine, 1961; 1031; 1 Audio Reel(s) (Box 92)
  - The Princeton University Glee Club - 1960-1961 season recording session, 1147; 3 Audio Reel(s) (Box 96-97)
    ORIGINAL (not equalized). 1/4 inch magnetic tape, 7-inch reel.
  - The Princeton University Glee Club - 1961 season recording session, 1150; 4 Audio Reel(s) (Box 97)
    Created by Carillon Records. 1/4 inch magnetic tape, 7-inch reel.
  - The Princeton University Glee Club with Yale Glee Club - Princeton-Yale Football Concert, 1961; 1187; 4 Audio Reel(s) (Box 99-100)
  - The Princeton University Glee Club with Smith College Choirs - Advent Vespers, 1961; 1224; 1 Phonograph Record(s) (Box 61)
    Created by Vogt Quality Recordings. 33 1/3 rpm album.
  - The Princeton University Glee Club with Wellesley College Choir and Chamber Orchestra - Haydn: Missa in tempore belli ("Paukenmesse"), 1961; 1227; 1 Phonograph Record(s) (Box 61)
  - The Nassoons, 1961; AR.2006.077; 2187; 1 Phonograph Record(s) (Box 213)
  - The Princeton University Chapel Choir - Christmas Vespers ("Angelus Ad Virginem"), 1962; 954; 1 Audio Reel(s) (Box 86)
  - The Princeton University Chapel Choir with Radcliffe Choral Society and Riverside Chamber Singers - Milbank - Des Prez: Ave Maria, Lassus: Hieremiae Prophetae Lamentatione, Schutz: Musicalische Exequien (German Requiem), 1962; 974; 1 Audio Reel(s) (Box 88)
  - The Princeton University Chapel Choir with Radcliffe, 1962; 1011; 3 Audio Reel(s) (Box 90-91)
  - The Princeton University Chapel Choir - Easter Concert - Lassus: Adoramus Te, Schutz: Der Herr 1st Gross, 1962; 1027; 2 Audio Reel(s) (Box 92)
  - The Princeton University Chapel Choir - Sunday Anthems - Lassus: Oculus non Videt, 1962; 1032; 1 Audio Reel(s) (Box 92)
  - The Princeton University Glee Club with the Princeton University Orchestra and Bryn Mawr College Chorus - Beethoven: Christus Am Oelberge, Oratorium (Opus 85), 1962; 1226; 1 Phonograph Record(s) (Box 61)
  - The Princeton University Glee Club with the Choir and Augmented Chorus of Mary Baldwin College - Bach: Magnificat, Purcell: Come Ye Sons of Art, 1962; 1229; 1 Phonograph Record(s) (Box 61)
  - The Princeton University Chapel Choir with Radcliffe Choral Society and Riverside Singers - Milbank - Des Prez: Ave Maria, Lassus: Lamentations of Jeremiah, Schutz: Musicalische Exequien (A German Requiem), circa 1962; 1237; 1 Phonograph Record(s) (Box 61)
  - The Princeton Nassoons, 1963; AR.2002.010; 920; 1 Phonograph Record(s) (Box 61)
  - The Eight Balls - Class of 1938 Jazz Band "The Eight Balls" - 25th Reunion, 1963; 921; 1 Phonograph Record(s) (Box 60)
  - The Princeton University Chapel Choir - Christmas Vespers, 1963; 955; 1 Audio Reel(s) (Box 86)
  - The Princeton University Chapel Choir with Vassar College Choir - Milbank - Bach: Contata No. 150, Contata No. 106, 1963; 975; 2 Audio Reel(s) (Box 88)
  - The Princeton University Chapel Choir - Motet Concert - Akaujo: Tiento, Cabanillesi: Passacaglia, Seixas: Toccata in C-Major, 1963; 1025; 2 Audio Reel(s) (Box 92)
    organ soloists: Rothrock, Fehl. 1/4 inch magnetic tape, 7-inch reel.
  - The Princeton University Chapel Choir - Sunday Anthems 1963-1963 - Des Prez: O Domine, 1033; 1 Audio Reel(s) (Box 92)
  - The Princeton University Chapel Choir - Sunday Anthems - Byrd: Iustorum Animae (F), 1963; 1034; 1 Audio Reel(s) (Box 92)
  - The Princeton University Chapel Choir - Milbank - Handel: Funeral Anthem, Mozart: Missa brevis, 1964; 977; 2 Audio Reel(s) (Box 88)
  - The Princeton University Chapel Choir - Christmas Concert, 1964; 1004; 1 Audio Reel(s) (Box 90)
  - The Princeton University Chapel Choir - excerpts from Motet Concert, 1964; 1023; 1 Audio Reel(s) (Box 91)
  - The Princeton University Chapel Choir - Easter Concert - Morales: O Magnum Mysterium, 1964; 1024; 1 Audio Reel(s) (Box 92)
  - The Princeton University Chapel Choir - Sunday Anthems 1963-1964 - Lassus: Adoramus Te, 1035; 1 Audio Reel(s) (Box 92)
  - The Princeton University Glee Club with Chatham College Choir - Pittsburgh, 1964; 1130; 3 Audio Reel(s) (Box 95)
    Walter Nollner, Conductor. 1/4 inch magnetic tape, 7-inch reel.
  - The Princeton University Chapel Choir with Wellesley College Choir - Milbank - Handel: Funeral Anthem on the Death of Queen Caroline, 1964; 1240; 1 Phonograph Record(s) (Box 61)
    Vol. 1 - Milbank Memorial - C.Weinrich, Conductor. 33 1/3 rpm album.
  - The Princeton Nassoons' 25th Anniversary Album, 1964; AR.2006.077; 2184; 1 Phonograph Record(s) (Box 213)
  - The Princeton Nassoons' 25th Anniversary Album, 1964; 2184; 1 Phonograph Record(s) (Box 213)
    Copy. 33 1/3 rpm album.
  - The Princeton Nassoons 25th Anniversary Album, 1964; AR.2013.072; 2370; 1 Phonograph Record(s) (Box 213)
    Created by Princeton Nassoons. 35 mm.
  - The Princeton University Glee Club - "Bach to Old Nassau", circa 1964; 1230; 1 Phonograph Record(s) (Box 61)
  - The Princeton University Chapel Choir - Milbank - Jubilate Deo (in D), Haydn: Mass in B-Flat, My Heart is Inditing, Christmas Concert, 1965; 945; 2 Audio Reel(s) (Box 85-86)
  - The Princeton University Chapel Choir - Motet Concert, 1965; 1005; 1 Audio Reel(s) (Box 90)
  - The Princeton University Chapel Choir - Motet Concert, 1965; 1005; 1 Audio Reel(s) (Box 91)
  - The Princeton University Chapel Choir - "#1 1964-1965", 1006; 1 Audio Reel(s) (Box 90)
  - Chamber Chorus - The Princeton University Glee Club and the Princeton University Chapel Choir - Festival d'Aix en Provence - Monteverdi: "Gloria," Schutz: Das Vaterunser, 1965; 1066; 1 Audio Reel(s) (Box 94)
  - Smith-Princeton Chamber Chorus - European Tour - Monteverdi: Gloria, Imbrie: Two Christmas Carols, Schutz: Das Vaterunser, My Lord What a Morning, The Battle of Jericho, London: Osanna, Charpentier: In Nativitatem Domini Nostri Jesu Christi Canticum, 1965; 1139; 2 Audio Reel(s) (Box 96)
  - The Princeton University Glee Club with the Vassar College Choir, 1965; 1142; 1 Audio Reel(s) (Box 96)
    at Princeton. 1/4 inch magnetic tape, 7-inch reel.
  - The Princeton University Glee Club with the Vassar College Choir - The Christmas Music, 1965; 1143; 1 Audio Reel(s) (Box 96)
    at Vassar. 1/4 inch magnetic tape, 7-inch reel.
  - The Princeton University Glee Club with Yale Glee Club, 1965; 1186; 1 Audio Reel(s) (Box 99)
  - Princeton University Glee Club and Smith College Glee Club -- Joint Concert, 1965; 1218; 1 Phonograph Record(s) (Box 61)
    Honoring the 90th Year of Paul Bedford '97\n\nBach: Missa brevis in G-Major (BWV236), Purcell: Selections from "The Fairy Queen," Walter Nollner - Princeton Conductor, Iva Dee Hiatt - Smith Conductor, assisted by Princeton Chamber Orchestra. Created by Kenneth Raymond Wight Associates. 33 1/3 rpm album.
  - Princeton University Glee Club and Smith College Glee Club -- Joint Concert, 1965; AR.2003.036; 1218; 1 Disc(s) (Box 212)
    Honoring the 90th Year of Paul Bedford '97\n\nBach: Missa brevis in G-Major (BWV236), Purcell: Selections from "The Fairy Queen," Walter Nollner - Princeton Conductor, Iva Dee Hiatt - Smith Conductor, assisted by Princeton Chamber Orchestra. Compact disc.
  - Smith-Princeton Chamber Chorus - "The Smith-Princeton Chamber Chorus in Europe Summer 1965", 1222; 2 Phonograph Record(s) (Box 61)
  - The Princeton University Chapel Choir - Christmas Vespers, 1966; 956; 1 Audio Reel(s) (Box 86)
    Carl Weinrich, Conductor. 1/4 inch magnetic tape, 7-inch reel.
  - The Princeton University Chapel Choir - Mozart: Mass in C (Credo), 1966; 1010; 1 Audio Reel(s) (Box 90)
  - The Princeton University Chapel Choir - Motet Concert, 1966; 1017; 2 Audio Reel(s) (Box 91)
  - The Princeton University Glee Club with the Columbus Boychoir and Chamber Orchestra, 1966; 1141; 1 Audio Reel(s) (Box 96)
  - The Princeton University Glee Club with the Goucher College Glee Club, 1966; 1144; 1 Audio Reel(s) (Box 96)
  - The Princeton University Chapel Choir with Sarah Lawrence Chorus - Milbank, 1966; 1236; 1 Phonograph Record(s) (Box 61)
    Milbank Memorial - C.Weinrich, Conductor - unopened. 33 1/3 rpm album.
  - Nassoons Records, 1966; AR.2015.108; 2392; 1 Phonograph Record(s) (Box 213)
  - The Princeton University Glee Club with the Princeton University Russian Band- Gregorian chant, Des Prez: Motet Ave coelorum Domina, four Russian folk songs, circa 1966; 1173; 1 Audio Reel(s) (Box 98)
    W.Nollner, Conductor - Paul Rodzianko '67, Russian band leader. 1/4 inch magnetic tape, 7-inch reel.
  - 45th Edition of The Follies of 1922 - featuring Forgan and Tilden, 1967; 879; 2 Phonograph Record(s) (Box 60)
    recorded at 45th reunion. 33 1/3 rpm album.
  - The Princeton University Chapel Choir - Christmas Vespers, 1967; 947; 1 Audio Reel(s) (Box 86)
  - The Princeton University Glee Club with Smith College Chorus and Chamber Orchestra - A Concert of Early Music, 1967; 1117; 2 Audio Reel(s) (Box 124)
    Created by Orban Associates. 1/4 inch magnetic tape, 10 1/2-inch reel.
  - The Princeton University Glee Club with Wellesley College Choir and Cambridge Festival Orchestra - Verdi, Schubert, Haydn, 1967; 1219; 1 Phonograph Record(s) (Box 61)
    Third Dober Memorial Concert - recorded at Wellesley. Created by Vogt Quality Recordings. 33 1/3 rpm album.
  - The Princeton University Glee Club - 1966-1967 season, 1225; 2 Phonograph Record(s) (Box 61)
    2 copies in single sleeve. 33 1/3 rpm album.
  - The Princeton Tigertones, 1967-1968; 2352; 1 Phonograph Record(s) (Box 213)
  - The Princeton University Chapel Choir - Milbank - Music for Chorus and Brass Instruments - Milbank Memorian, 1968; 939; 2 Audio Reel(s) (Box 85)
    C. Weinrich, Conductor (Gabrieli: Canzona per Sonare #2, Canzon Septimi #2, In Ecclesis; Schutz: Ist nicht Ephraim mein teurer Sohn? (SWV40), Psalm 115, Bach: Cantata 118, Hindemith: Apparebit Repentina). Created by Elite Recordings, Inc. 1/4 inch magnetic tape, 7-inch reel.
  - The Princeton University Chapel Choir - Bach, Hindemith (first movement), 1968; 1009; 1 Audio Reel(s) (Box 90)
  - The Princeton University Glee Club with Smith College Chorus - in Berlin - Schubert: Gesang der Geister Uber den Wassern, Rierenberg: Fire Flood and Olive Tree, London: Four Proverbs, 1968; 1099; 2 Audio Reel(s) (Box 95)
    Reels 2 and 3 only (Reel 1 missing). 1/4 inch magnetic tape, 7-inch reel.
  - Smith-Princeton Chamber Chorus - European Tour, 1968; 1114; 2 Audio Reel(s) (Box 124)
    Boxes labeled "Schubert - Glee Club Princeton - 2/25/1968". 1/4 inch magnetic tape, 10 1/2-inch reel.
  - Smith-Princeton Chamber Chorus - London: Four Proverbs, Schutz: Nun Danket Alle Gott, 1968; 1137; 1 Audio Reel(s) (Box 96)
    recorded at Chartres Cathedral, summer 1968. 1/4 inch magnetic tape, 7-inch reel.
  - Smith-Princeton Chamber Chorus - European Tour, 1968; 1145; 1 Audio Reel(s) (Box 102)
  - Nassoons Records, 1968; AR.2015.108; 2392; 1 Phonograph Record(s) (Box 213)
  - Princeton University Orchestra, 1969; AR.2000.096; 815; 1 Disc(s) (Box 50)
  - Princeton University Orchestra at Woolworth Center, 1969; AR.2000.096; 816; 1 Disc(s) (Box 50)
  - The Princeton University Glee Club with Vassar College Choir - Bach: Johannes-Passion (St.John Passion), 1969; 1169; 1 Audio Reel(s) (Box 98)
  - The Princeton University Glee Club with Wellesley College Choir - Handl, Kodaly, Bartok, Mozart, Schubert: Mass in A-Major, 1969; 1174; 2 Audio Reel(s) (Box 98)
  - The Princeton University Glee Club with Yale Glee Club, 1969; 1194; 3 Audio Reel(s) (Box 100)
    Includes Haydn, Mozart, Williams. 1/4 inch magnetic tape, 7-inch reel.
  - The Princeton University Chapel Choir?, 1969; 1232; 2 Audio Reel(s) (Box 127)
    Created by Buhler Recording. 1/4 inch magnetic tape, 10 1/2-inch reel; Duration: 83min.
  - The Prospective Sound, 1970; 691; 1 Phonograph Record(s) (Box 60)
  - Princeton University Orchestra with John Bogart and Shirley Sudock, 1970; AR.2000.096; 805; 1 Disc(s) (Box 50)
  - Graduate Student Composers' Concert, 1970; AR.2000.096; 806; 2 Disc(s) (Box 50)
  - Irene Schreier, 1970; AR.2000.096; 807; 2 Disc(s) (Box 50)
  - James Winn, 1970; AR.2000.096; 808; 1 Disc(s) (Box 50)
  - Opera Theatre - Mozart: The Abduction From the Seraglio, 1970; AR.2000.096; 809; 2 Disc(s) (Box 50)
  - Theatre in Time, 1970; AR.2000.096; 810; 2 Disc(s) (Box 50)
  - Geoffrey Michaels, 1970; AR.2000.096; 817; 2 Disc(s) (Box 50)
  - Joel Lester, 1970; AR.2000.096; 818; 2 Disc(s) (Box 50)
  - Princeton University Orchestra - John Witherspoon School, Princeton, 1970; AR.2000.096; 819; 1 Disc(s) (Box 50)
  - Michael Schub and Todd Fansler, 1970; AR.2000.096; 820; 2 Disc(s) (Box 50)
  - Norman Flitt and Elizabeth Grottle, 1970; AR.2000.096; 821; 1 Disc(s) (Box 50)
  - Jayn Seigel and Cheryl Seltzer, 1970; AR.2000.096; 822; 1 Disc(s) (Box 50)
  - Student Recital -- Nancy Lambert, Jane Strong, James Carmichael, Jeffrey Gall, Carly Emerson, Jeans Sachs, 1970; AR.2000.096; 823; 1 Disc(s) (Box 50)
  - Nadia Koutzen, 1970; AR.2000.096; 824; 2 Disc(s) (Box 50)
  - The Princeton University Glee Club - Brahms: Requiem, 1970; 1113; 1 Audio Reel(s) (Box 124)
    Richardson Auditorium - Walter Nollner, Conductor. 1/4 inch magnetic tape, 10 1/2-inch reel.
  - The Princeton University Glee Club with the Manhattanville College Glee Club - Brahms: Ein Deutches Requiem, 1970; 1231; 2 Phonograph Record(s) (Box 61)
    Walter Nollner, Conductor. Created by Vogt Quality Recordings. 33 1/3 rpm album.
  - The Princeton University Glee Club with Yale Glee Club, 1971; AR.2000.096; 772; 2 Disc(s) (Box 48)
  - Jerry Kuderna and Chester Brezniak, 1971; AR.2000.096; 773; 1 Disc(s) (Box 48)
  - Mimmi Fulmer, 1971; AR.2000.096; 774; 1 Disc(s) (Box 49)
  - Concert of Contemporary Music, 1971; AR.2000.096; 775; 1 Disc(s) (Box 49)
  - Edward Cone and Walter Noller, 1971; AR.2003.036; 776; 1 Disc(s) (Box 212)
    Franz Schubert -- Fantasie Op. 103, Variations in A flat Op. 35, Grande Duo Op. 140. Compact disc.
  - Edward Cone and Walter Noller, 1971; AR.2000.096; 776; 2 Disc(s) (Box 49)
  - Opera Theatre - Hamilton-Murray Theatre, 1971; AR.2000.096; 777; 1 Disc(s) (Box 49)
  - Stuart Surick, 1971; AR.2000.096; 782; 1 Disc(s) (Box 49)
  - The Princeton University Glee Club with Sarah Lawrence College Chorus, 1971; AR.2000.096; 783; 2 Disc(s) (Box 49)
  - Elizabeth Grottle-Strebel and Clark Feldman, 1971; AR.2000.096; 784; 1 Disc(s) (Box 49)
  - Princeton University Orchestra, 1971; AR.2000.096; 785; 1 Disc(s) (Box 49)
    Richardson Auditorium. Compact disc.
  - Princeton University Orchestra at New Jersey State Museum Auditorium, Trenton, NJ, 1971; AR.2000.096; 786; 1 Disc(s) (Box 49)
  - Orchestra Chamber Ensemble -- Wilcox Hall, 1971; AR.2000.096; 787; 1 Disc(s) (Box 49)
  - Orchestra Chamber Ensemble -- Princeton Inn College Theatre, 1971; AR.2000.096; 788; 1 Disc(s) (Box 49)
  - Band - Concert Band, 1971; AR.2000.096; 789; 1 Disc(s) (Box 49)
  - Graduate Student Composers, 1971; AR.2000.096; 790; 1 Disc(s) (Box 49)
  - Chamber Chorus - Smith-Princeton Chamber Chorus, 1971; AR.2000.096; 791; 1 Disc(s) (Box 49)
  - American Society of University Composers, 1971; AR.2000.096; 792; 1 Disc(s) (Box 49)
  - Princeton University Orchestra, 1971; AR.2000.096; 793; 1 Disc(s) (Box 49)
  - Chamber Chorus - A Concert of Chamber Music, 1971; AR.2000.096; 794; 1 Disc(s) (Box 49)
  - Princeton University Orchestra at Richardson Auditorium, 1971; AR.2000.096; 795; 1 Disc(s) (Box 49)
  - Princeton University Orchestra, 1971; AR.2000.096; 796; 1 Disc(s) (Box 49)
  - Fadlou Shehadi, 1971; AR.2000.096; 797; 1 Disc(s) (Box 49)
  - Helen Harbison, 1971; AR.2000.096; 798; 1 Disc(s) (Box 49)
  - Jean Thomas, 1971; AR.2000.096; 799; 1 Disc(s) (Box 49)
  - Annual Symposium -- Faculty Compositions, 1971; AR.2000.096; 800; 1 Disc(s) (Box 49)
  - Norman Flitt, 1971; AR.2000.096; 801; 1 Disc(s) (Box 49)
  - Robert Helps, 1971; AR.2000.096; 802; 1 Disc(s) (Box 50)
  - Chamber Chorus - Da Capo Chamber Players, 1971; AR.2000.096; 803; 1 Disc(s) (Box 50)
  - John Sessions, 1971; AR.2000.096; 804; 1 Disc(s) (Box 50)
  - Undergraduate Composers Rehearsal and Concert, 1971; AR.2000.096; 811; 1 Disc(s) (Box 50)
  - Student Concert - Vera Basch and James Carmichael, 1971; AR.2000.096; 812; 1 Disc(s) (Box 50)
  - Geoffrey Michaels, 1971; AR.2000.096; 813; 2 Disc(s) (Box 50)
  - Shirlee Emmons, 1971; AR.2000.096; 814; 1 Disc(s) (Box 50)